sailogy.com 2013-11-04

# Privacy Policy - Sailogy.com: 2,000 boats for rent | Sailing holidays in Italy, Croatia, Greece.

### Privacy Policy, as per Italian D. Lgs 30.06.2003 N. 196, Art. 13

Sailogy is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement. Sailogy may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page every time you visit this website to ensure that you are happy with any changes.

### Handling of the data

The handling of the personal data is carried out to ensuring that your information is secure and private, and is carried out with manual and electronic means to memorize, handle and forward the data. Personal data will be handled following proper standards, collected and registered for specific purposes, explicit and legitimate, exact and, if necessary, appropriate, complete and not exceeding the standards requested to fulfill the obligation, stored in a way that will allow to recognize the individual only for a period of time not exceeding the time required to fulfill the obligation for which they have originally been collected and subsequently handled.

### Data provided voluntarily by users

Sailogy collects personal information and other data, which are submitted by users voluntarily via web or mobile registration forms, as well as forwarded to the Company via mail or email in an explicit and voluntary way. Such data may concern essential information required to carry out the service requested by the user (i.e. Newsletter) and/or to contact the user (name, mail address, any other personal data inserted in the letter). The optional, explicit and voluntary forwarding of emails to the address given on this site, implies the acquisition of the email address, essential to reply to the requests, and of any other additional personal data in the communication.

### Surfing data collected by electronic means.

Information systems and software procedures for the correct functioning of the Sailogy web and mobile sites acquire, during normal use, personal data, whose transmission is implicit in the use of internet communication protocols (i.e. user IP address or domain name of the computer used to access the web, URL of the requested resources, time of request or session time, server submitted query method used, files’ size received as request response, numeric code concerning the status of the server response and other kind of information related to the operating system and the user IT environment). The Sailogy website uses technologies like cookies, to collect statistical information on the use of the web (i.e. total number of visitors on the sites, number of visitors per single page, name of the domain of origin of visitors’ internet services supplier) and to improve the surfing experience.

### Cookies

During surfing of the Sailogy website, information is collected through files called "cookies", which help to identify your computer or browser. A cookie is an encrypted string of text stored on your computer or on the mobile phone, to be able to recognize it quickly the next time. In the case of Mobile site cookies, the latter memorize only name, surname and booking number. In the case of computer cookies, these allow a customization of an internet website, to make surfing smoother and an improved display of most requested information by quantitative check-out of web pages access. Cookies used do not memorize personal data except the IP address. Cookies retained information is anonymous and remain so as the cookie identification number is not associated to personal data supplied by surfers. You may always disenable cookies by changing your browser settings.

### Why we collect the data

Sailogy collects the necessary personal data of the users to carry out authorization, habilitation and personalization of accesses to the various areas and contents of the Company’s website. Furthermore, Sailogy collects the necessary data to fulfill the booking, deriving from booking processes and purchases of travel means. We require this information to provide you with this service, giving access to the data to operational and commercial Sailogy staff, and to the charter companies that will provide the charter services.  
The personal and/or sensitive data given or acquired during the website navigation may be given, in the measure requested to carry out the service, to: Internal Sailogy personnel with the intent of improving our products and services (as per D.Lgs 196/2003); Third party companies, such as charter companies, carrying out services which are essential towards Sailogy operations.   
With reference to sensitive data, these may be handled even without explicit consent of the person as per art. 26, n.4, D. Lgs 196/2003. However these data will not be distributed. Be reminded that from time to time (not as part of the ordinary management of this website) the Authorities may request information and details as per art. 157 of D. Lgs. 196/2003, to check on the management of personal data. In these instances, Sailogy is obliged to comply to avoid a fine. Sailogy as "Owner" of the relative data management, informs that the data will be handled and used exclusively as per purposes highlighted in this communication.

### Exercising your rights

The Customers can contact Sailogy in order to exercise their rights as prescribed by article 7 "Access to personal data and other rights" of Legislative decree 196/2003 no. 196. To exercise these rights, passengers must also send communication to the following e-mail address: info@sailogy.com. If you no longer wish to receive communications from Sailogy, please follow send an email to info@sailogy.com.

### Right to access your personal data

Sailogy clients may request details of personal information held, to the Owner and/or data Manager, under art. 7 "Right to access personal data" of D. Lgs. 196/2003 n.196. List of people in charge of personal data handling. Compulsory information as per art.13 letter f Law Decree DLGS/196/2003.

Manlio Accardo, CEO of TSH Srl.
